{
    "id": "40b1b13dc8634e9db9a92295c2e64806",
    "title": "Prepositions of Time | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I usually get up ………………… six o’clock.",
            "description": "We use at with clock times.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "198e9a17a3974a42a068307744da27e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Phone me ……………… lunchtime.",
            "description": "We use at with clock times.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e70964b082e5415a87c9f401c1e9d8a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I work best ………………. the evening.",
            "description": "We use ‘in’ with parts of the day. For example, we say in the morning, in the afternoon and in the evening. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2753f107003b4b7fbd8ed7fde13308c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I usually go for a walk ……………….. the morning.",
            "description": "We use ‘in’ with parts of the day. For example, we say in the morning, in the afternoon and in the evening. ",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8b18fe4027c947b28cec40ba0326b571"
        },
        {
            "question": "We met …………….. a cold afternoon in winter.",
            "description": "We use ‘on’ when we say which morning / afternoon / etc., we are talking about.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ae017e1c570046a5af53f1371257c31d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will call you ……………. Sunday.",
            "description": "We use ‘on’ with days.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a9cf349c57b447d981430448417f10ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are you doing …………….. the weekend?",
            "description": "We can say at the weekend or on the weekend.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9896fc559a524af38afb1a6b5ef72d7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "They got married ……………… the week after Easter.",
            "description": "We use in for longer periods.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bfd92adb1eaf4e038e43590eea39af34"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are having the house painted …………… Easter.",
            "description": "We use ‘at’ to talk about the whole of the holidays at Christmas, Easter etc.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "58e90d6beb2c4cab9bd55042a2dc6fc2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wrote the book …………. a month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "af97d3943302446497be76dd71789866"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you free .......................?",
            "description": "Prepositions are not used in expressions of time before next, last, this, that, each, every etc.",
            "answers": [
                "in this evening",
                "this evening",
                "on this evening"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "65093657181d448d84ea2ab705e13ce2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s meet ………………",
            "description": "Prepositions are not used in expressions of time before next, last, this, that, each, every etc.",
            "answers": [
                "on one day",
                "in one day",
                "one day"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "904348d029874d52883d35ce131df189"
        }
    ]
}